Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series XVII. Parking
  - Parking - Law (1), 1946-1947 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Parking - Law (2), 1949-1952 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Parking - Law - U.S. (Oversized), 1950 (Box 70)
  - Parking - U.S. - Arkansas, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Bakersfield (Oversized), 1947 (Box 61)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Glendale, 1950-1957 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Los Angeles, 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Oakland, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Pasadena, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Sacramento, 1947-1966 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - San Diego, 1950-1958 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - San Francisco, 1946-1959 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Miscellaneous (1), 1946-1950 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Parking - U.S. - California - Miscellaneous (2), 1951-1960 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Parking - U.S. - Illinois- Chicago (Oversized), 1963 (Box 62)
  - Parking - U.S. - Nevada - Reno (Oversized), 1950 (Box 69)
- Series XVIII. Parks
  - Parks - Municipal - District of Columbia, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Parks - Municipal - Illinois, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Parks - Municipal - Iowa (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Parks - Municipal - Maryland (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Parks - Municipal - Massachusetts, 1920,1940 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Parks - Municipal - Minnesota, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Parks - Municipal - Michigan (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Parks - Municipal - Minnesota, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Parks - Municipal - Missouri, 1940-1950 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Parks - Municipal - New Jersey, 1940 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Parks - Municipal - New Jersey, 1930 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Parks - Municipal - New York, 1930,1940,1960 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Parks - Municipal - New York, 1930-1950 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Parks - Municipal - New York, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Parks - Municipal - New York, 1940-1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Parks - Municipal - Oklahoma, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Parks - Municipal - Pennsylvania, 1920-1940 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Parks - Municipal - Pennsylvania, 1930-1950 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Parks - Municipal - Ohio (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Parks - Municipal - Ohio (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Parks - Municipal - Ohio (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Parks - Municipal - Rhode Island, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Parks - Municipal - Tennessee, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Parks - Municipal - Texas, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Parks - Municipal - Utah, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Parks - Municipal - Virginia, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Parks - Municipal - Washington, 1945 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Parks - Foreign - Canada, 1940-1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Parks - Foreign - Netherland (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Parks - Foreign - Sweden, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Parks - Equipment, 1910,1940 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Series XIX. Population
  - Population - General, 1930-1940 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Population - General, 1940-1950 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Population - General, 1940-1950 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Population - General, 1950-1960 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Population - Migration, 1940,1960 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Population - Migration - Arkansas, 1943 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Population - Migration - California, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Population - Migration - Connecticut (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Population - District of Columbia (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Population - Migration - Georgia, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Population - Migration - Illinois, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Population - Migration - Indiana, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Population - Migration, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Population - Migration - Kansas, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Population - Migration - Maine, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Population - Migration - Maryland, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Population - Migration - Massachusetts, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Population - Migration, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Population - Migration - Missouri, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Population - Migration - New Jersey, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Population - Migration - New York State, 1940-1950 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Population - Migration - Ohio, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Population - Migration - Oklahoma, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Population - Migration - Pennsylvania, 1940,1960 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Population - Migration - South Carolina, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Population - Migration - Tennessee, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Population - Migration - Texas, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Population - Migration - Virginia, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Population - Migration - Washington State, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Population - Migration - Wisconsin, 1942 (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Population - United States, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Population - U.S. - Arkansas, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Population - U.S. - Arkansas, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Population - U.S. - Arkansas, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Population - U.S. - Arkansas, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Population - U.S. - California, 957 (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Population - U.S. - California, 1950 (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Population - U.S. - California, 1950-1960 (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Population - U.S. - California, 1940-1960 (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Population - U.S. - Colorado, 1950-1960 (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Population - U.S. - Connecticut, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Population - U.S. - Connecticut, 1941 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Population - U.S. - District of Columbia, 1950-1960 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Population - U.S. - Florida, 1950-1960 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Population - U.S. - Georgia, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Population - Hawaii, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Population - U.S. - Illinois, 1940-1960 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Population - U.S. - Indiana, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Population - U.S. - Indiana, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Population - U.S. - Kansas, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Population - U.S. - Kentucky, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Population - U.S. - Maryland, 1930-1950 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Population - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1940-1970 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Population - U.S. - Michigan, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Population - U.S. - Michigan, 1950-1960 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Population - U.S. - New Hamshire, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Population - U.S. - Missouri, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Population - U.S. - New Hamshire, 1940,1960 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1930-1940 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1940-1950 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Population - U.S. - New Jersey, 1950-1960 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1930-1940 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State - New York City, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State - New York City, 1940-1950 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Population - U.S. - New York State - New York City, 1940-1950 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Population - U.S. - North Carolina, 1940-1950 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Population - U.S. - North Dakota, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Population - U.S. - Ohio, 1940-1960 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Population - U.S. - Oklahoma, 1940-1950 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Population - U.S. - Oregon, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Population - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1930-1950 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Population - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1950-1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Population - U.S. - Rhode Island, 1940-1980 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Population - U.S.Tennessee, 1941 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Population - U.S. - Texas, 1940-1950 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Population - U.S. - Virginia, 1940,1960 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Population - U.S. - Washington State, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Population - U.S. - Virginia, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Population - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1940-1960 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Population - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Population - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Population - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Population - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Population - Foreign - Canada, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Population - Foregin - Great Britain, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Population - Foreign - Virginia Island, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Population - Foreign - South America, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Series XX. Preservation
  - Preservation - Maryland - Annapolis (Oversized), 1959 (Box 62)
  - Preservation - New York, 1960-1970 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Preservation - Preservation, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Preservation - New York - Newsletter, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Preservation - New York - N.Y.C. (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Preservation - North Carolina (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Preservation - Pennsylvania, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Preservation - Puerto Rico (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Preservation - Rhode Island, 1960-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Preservation - Rhode Island, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Preservation - South Carolina, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Preservation - Tennessee - Memphis (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Preservation - Texas, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Preservation - Texas, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Preservation - Virginia Island (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Preservation - Virginia, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Preservation - Virginia, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Preservation - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Preservation - Canada (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Preservation - Europe, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Foreign - Great Britain, 1940-1950 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Preservation - Legislation - General, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Preservation - Legislation - General, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Preservation - Legislation - U.S, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Alabama, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Arizona (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Arkansas, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Preservation - Legislation - California (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Colorado, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Delaware, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Florida, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Hawaii, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Idaho, 1940,1960 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Illinois, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Indiana, 1930.1950 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Iowa (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Kentucky (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Louisiana, 1930-1970 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Maryland, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Massachusetts, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Michigan (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Minnesota (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Mississippi, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Missouri (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Montana, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Nebraska (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Nevada, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Preservation - Legislation - New Jersey (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Preservation - Legislation - New Jersey (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Preservation - Legislation - New Mexico, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Preservation - Legislation - New York-Arch Review (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Preservation - Legislation - New York, 1940-1960 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Preservation - Legislation - North Carolina (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Ohio (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Oklahoma, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Oregon, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Pennsylvania (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Puerto Rico (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Rhode Island (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Preservation - Legislation - South Carolina (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Preservation - Legislation - South Dakota (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Tennessee, 1950-1960 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Texas (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Utah (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Vermont (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Virgin Island (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Virginia (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Washington (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Wisconsin (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Preservation - Legislation - Wyoming (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Preservation - Surveys - General (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Preservation - Surveys - California, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Preservation - Surveys - District of Columbia, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - Preservation - Surveys - U.S. - Georgia, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - Preservation - Surveys - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - Preservation - Surveys - U.S. - Maryland (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Preservation - Surveys - New Jersey - Cape May (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Preservation - Surveys - U.S. - New York (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Preservation - General (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Preservation - General (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Preservation - General (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Preservation - U.S. - Historic Trust, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Preservation - Periodicals, 1970-1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Preservation - U.S. - National Trust (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Preservation - Alabama (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Preservation - Arizona, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Preservation - Arkansas (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Preservation - California, 1950 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Preservation - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Preservation - District of Columbia, 1950-1960 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Preservation - Florida (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Preservation - Georgia (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Preservation - Hawaii, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Preservation - Illinois, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Preservation - Iowa, 1910,1960 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Preservation - Iowa, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Preservation - Kentucky, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Preservation - Louisiana, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Preservation - Louisiana, 1950-1970 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Preservation - Maine, 1960-1070 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Preservation - Maryland (1), 1970 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Preservation - Maryland (2) (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Preservation - Maryland (3) (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Preservation - Maryland (4) (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Preservation - Maryland - Annapolis (Oversized), 1959 (Box 70)
  - Preservation - Massachusetts, 1950-1970 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Preservation - Minnesota, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Preservation - Mississippi, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Preservation - Preservation, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Preservation - Nevada (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Preservation - New Hampshire (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Preservation - New Jersey - Cape May (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Preservation - New Mexico, 1960-1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Series XXI. Public Buildings
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1920,1960 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - California, 1910,1940-1950 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - California, 1940-1960 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Connecticut (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - District of Columbia, 1930 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Hawaii, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Iowa, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Michigan, 1920,1940-1950 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Michigan (Oversized), 1958 (Box 62)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - New Jersey, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - New York, 1920-1960 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - North Carolina, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Ohio (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Oregon, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Texas, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Virginia, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Washington, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Public Buildings - U.S. - Wisconsin (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Public Buildings - Foreign - Canada, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Public Buildings - Foreign - England, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Public Buildings - General, 1930-1940 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Public Buildings - General, 1930-1960 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Public Buildings - General, 1930-1950 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Public Buildings - General, 1930,1960 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Series XXII. Public Finance
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Arkansas, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Colorado, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Florida, 1930-1940 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Illinois, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Maryland, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Maryland, 1940-1960 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1938 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Michigan, 1940-1950 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - New York, 1930-1940 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - New York, 1940-1950,70 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Ohio, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1940 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Public Finance - South Carolina, 1930-1940 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Tennessee, 1950-1960 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Public Finance - U.S. - Vermont, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Public Finance - Foreign - Australia (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Public Finance - Foreign - Canada, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Public Finance - Foreign - Ethiopia, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Public Finance - Foreign - New Zealand, 1943 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Public Finance - Tax Delinquency, 1930-1940 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Public Finance - Tax Delinquency, 1930-1950 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Public Finance - Tax Delinquency, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Public Finance - Tax Delinquency - Michigan, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Public Finance - Tax Delinquency - N.Y.S, 1930-1940 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Series XXIII. Public Utilities
  - Public Utilities - General, 1930,50,60 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - Colorado, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - New Jersey, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - New York, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - Tennessee, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - Tennessee, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Public Utilities - U.S. - Washington, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Public Utilities - Electric Power General, 1920,1940 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Public Utilities - Electric Power - Florida, 1936 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Public Utilities - Electric Power - New York, 1929 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Public Utilities - Electric Power - T.V.A, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Public Utilities - Gas - General, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Public Utilities - Gas - General, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Public Utilities - Plans - Alabama, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Public Utilities - Plans - New York, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Series XXIV. Public Works
  - Public Works - U.S., 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Public Works - U.S. - California (Oversized), 1942 (Box 61)
  - Public Works - U.S. - District of Columbia, 1930,1960 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Illinois, 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Illinois, 1950-1960 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Illinois (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Indiana, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Mississippi, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Public Works - U.S. - New York, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Public Works - U.S. - New York, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1910-1920 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Public Works - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1910-1920 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Public Works - Foreign - Brazil, 1950 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Public Works - Foreign - California, 1940-1950 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Series XXV. Rapid Transit
  - Rapid Transit - General, 1960-1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S., 1950-1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - California (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - California, 1950-1960 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Illinois, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Maryland, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Maryland - Baltimore (Oversized), 1965 (Box 70)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - New Jersey, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - New York, 1950-1960 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Ohio, 1950-1960 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Rapid Transit - U.S. - Washington, D.C, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Rapid Transit - Foreign - Canada, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Series XXVI. Recreation
  - Recreation - General (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Recreation - U.S. - California, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Colorado (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Georgia, 1950-1960 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Indiana (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Massachusetts, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Massachusetts (Oversized), 1949 (Box 62)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Michigan, 1920,60 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Recreation - U.S. - New Jersey (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Recreation - U.S. - New York, 1920,40,60 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Pennsylvania, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Rhode Island, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recreation - U.S. - South Carolina, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Recreation - U.S. - South Dakota, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Texas, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Tennessee, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Virginia (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Virginia (Oversized) (Box 70)
  - Recreation - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Recreation - Outdoor, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Recreation - Outdoor, 1950-1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Recreation - Outdoor, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Series XXVII. Regional Planning
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Belgium, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Canada (1), 1952-1962 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Canada (2), 1966-1968 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Denmark, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - France, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Regional Planning - Foreign - Germany, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 20)